knownsrv.com 2017-11-23

# KnownSRV | Secure, Quality, and Fast Hosting Solutions

KnownSRV Solutions respects the privacy and security of its customers and users of its website. KnownSRV strives to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers to you the information, products and services that you need. In order to achieve this goal, KnownSRV sometimes collects information during your visits to our website. 

**KnownSRV promises that:**  
\- We do not and will not offer for sale, share, or lease any information given to us by you, except as disclosed in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy").  
\- Our Privacy Policy applies to prospective, current, and former customers and users.

We have prepared this Privacy Policy to enable you to understand which personal identifying information of yours is collected, how and when we might use your information, how we protect your information, who has access to your information, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. This Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

**

### Information We Collect

**

KnownSRV collects certain information from and about its users in three ways: (I) from our web server logs, (II) with cookies and (III) directly from the user. 

Web server logs: When you visit our website, KnownSRV may collect "Non-Personally Identifiable" information to administer the site and analyze its usage, such as:  
\- Your Internet protocol address (explained below);  
\- The type of browser or computer you use;  
\- The number of links you click within our website;  
\- The state or country from which you accessed our website;  
\- The date and time of your visit;  
\- The name of your Internet service provider;  
\- The web page from which you linked to our website; and  
\- The pages you viewed on our website

**

### Internet Protocol ("IP") Address

**

An IP Address is a number assigned to your computer while using the Internet from which Web servers can automatically identify your computer. KnownSRV servers gather your IP address and the webpage from where you linked to our website. Your IP address assists KnownSRV in administering and optimizing the website for you, analyzing website usage, and diagnosing problems with the website.

**

### Cookies

**

Our website uses cookies (i.e., small bits of text that our servers place into a file on your computer's hard drive). We use cookies to save your preferences and login information, and provide personalized functionality. Cookies may also store Personally Identifiable Information (defined below) you have entered so that you do not have to continually reenter the same information. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings, but be aware that this will disable some of the functionality on the KnownSRV website.

**

### Personally Identifiable Information

**

On some pages of our website, users can register to purchase products or services, receive personalized content and participate in surveys or forums. When you register, KnownSRV may ask you for some personal information, which may include, but not limited to, your full name, postal address, phone number and email address. We may then contact you with information about KnownSRV products and services.

If you purchase products or services, we may also request financial information such as credit card or bank account information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the products and services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider.

**

### Additional Information

**

As a security measure and to ensure that our website and computer network remain available to all customers, KnownSRV may use software programs to monitor network traffic or to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. These software programs may also collect information regarding your use of our website and computer network.

You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide technical support assistance and information to you. For example, we may collect personal information from you (such as an e-mail address, system information and problem descriptions) in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting. If you choose to correspond with us through electronic communication (e.g. email, online chat or instant messaging), we may retain a copy of the electronic communication together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

**

### How We Use Your Information

**

KnownSRV uses the information we collect to notify you about your account and to notify you about changes to the terms and conditions governing your use of our website, products and services. We may also use the information we collect to notify you about other products and services we think you will find valuable and about special offers. You may notify us of your desire not to receive notifications relating to new products and services and special offers by "opting-out" as provided for below. Our employees, contractors, or agents will at times require access to your Personally Identifiable information. KnownSRV permits access to such information only for business purposes, such as administration and developing our products or services.

**

### Information Released

**

KnownSRV may release some customer Non-Personally Identifiable information, this website's traffic patterns, and related website usage information to our affiliates and reputable third parties on an aggregated basis. We take measures to select product or service providers that are responsible and afford similar privacy protections to their customers. However, we do not make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies.

KnownSRV may share or disclose Personally Identifiable information with agents and contractors who use such information on behalf of KnownSRV or in connection with administering or delivering products and services on behalf of KnownSRV.

**

### SPECIAL CASES OF RELEASE

**

Both Personally Identifiable and Non-Personally Identifiable information may be transferred to a third party: 1. As required by law, in a matter of public safety or policy, or as compelled by a court of law 2. In the event of a change of ownership or assets; and 3. To affiliated entities of common control, such as subsidiaries and parent companies. The use of your information by these affiliates of common control will comply with this Privacy Policy.

**

### Contacting You Directly

**

KnownSRV may contact you directly through the email address or other information you provide to confirm information or purchases we have successfully received from you. KnownSRV will also contact you to respond to your questions, to provide the services you request, to manage your account, and/or to inform you of any service announcements.

**

### Opt-Out Provision

**

If you don't want to receive promotional materials from KnownSRV, you may opt out at any time. You may "opt out" by contacting us at [privacy@KnownSRV.com](mailto:info@knownsrv.com). Upon properly opting-out, KnownSRV will take reasonable efforts to delete a user's personal information from its database. However, please note that it may be impossible to entirely delete a user's information because some residual information may reside on backups or records of deletions.

**

### Third Party Sites

**

The KnownSRV website includes links, ad banners, etc. to other websites which may or may not be affiliated with KnownSRV. Notwithstanding any affiliation, KnownSRV does NOT control and is NOT responsible for the information and/or content you provide to and transactions you engage in with such third party sites. Please be aware that the operators of these other websites may collect and use different information about you that is not consistent with KnownSRV's Privacy Policy. For any concerns as to the privacy of your information on these websites, please refer to their respective privacy policies.

**

### Children

**

In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), KnownSRV does not knowingly collect or solicit any Personally Identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13).

**

### How We Protect Your Information

**

KnownSRV has employed the use of electronic security measures to protect against the loss, theft, misuse, alteration, or unauthorized disclosure of your information submitted to our website. These measures include firewalls, use of passwords, anti-virus and detection software.

When we ask customers or users to provide financial information (such as a credit card number) that data is protected using Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") technology. However, please note that electronic communication (e.g. email, online chat or instant messaging) that you may send to us may not be secure unless we advise you in advance that security measures will be in place prior to your transmitting the information. For that reason, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as financial information, social security numbers or passwords to us through unsecured electronic communication.

**

### Content Placed In Public

**

Some pages of the KnownSRV website may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, news groups or instant messaging available to you. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas is public. You should exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these areas. Don't disclose information in these public forums that might be considered confidential such as financial information, social security numbers, passwords or email addresses. Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information on the bulletin boards or in the chat areas, that information and any substantive information disclosed in the communication can be collected and used by third parties. This could result in unsolicited messages from others who post on such sites and are beyond the control of KnownSRV.

You represent and warrant that posting content to any public area of the KnownSRV website will not infringe or violate the rights, including but not limited to intellectual property rights, such as copyrights, patents, trademarks and trade secrets and rights of privacy and publicity of any third party.

**

### Transfer of Data Abroad

**

If you are visiting KnownSRV website from a country other than the countries in which our servers are located (currently the Netherlands), the various communications will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting our website and communicating electronically with us, you consent to the processing and transfer of your data as set out in this Privacy Policy.

**

### How to Correct Inaccuracies

**

If you've registered with our website, you can access and update your information online at our forums and our account management system. Otherwise, you may contact us at [info@knownsrv.com](mailto:info@knownsrv.com). 

**

### Modifications to the Privacy Policy

**

KnownSRV hereby reserves the right to amend, alter, modify, replace or suspend this Privacy Policy, from time to time, in its sole discretion. All such changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective when posted on KnownSRV website.

**

### Questions or Concerns

**

If you have any comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact KnownSRV via email at [info@KnownSRV.com](mailto:info@knownsrv.com). Effective Date of This Privacy Policy This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 02, 2010.
